(Amy:)Very much like this one.
Mm.
(Dave:)I doubt it was
like this one.
(Dave:)I mean, he's a genius, and
I wasn't even smart enough
(Dave:)to figure out why my wife
always smelled of croissants.
(Amy:)What was the rest
of your question?
(Dave:)Do you think you could
introduce me to him?
(Amy:)Really?
(Amy:)You-you want me to introduce you
to my ex-boyfriend?
(Dave:)You're right,
it's-it's weird.
(Dave:)No, wait. Do it.
(Dave:)No. I changed my mind.
(Dave:)I'd be too nervous.
Oh! I don't know
what to do.
(Leonard:)Are we gonna be much longer?
(Leonard:)I really have
to go to the bathroom.
(Bernadette:)Right here.
(Raj:)37 minutes left
until the deadline.
(Sheldon:)Someone will show.
(Howard:)And no matter what happens,
this is still a fun experiment.
(Raj:)Not as fun as the night we
blew up grapes in the microwave.
(Raj:)We really have led full lives.
(Sheldon:)Someone will show.